theofficialboard.com 2013-03-17

# Privacy Policy - TheOfficialBoard

**Introduction**

The Editor is committed to respecting and to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for the website. We respect the privacy of our users and shall not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor shall it permit anyone else to do so.

**Coverage**

TheOfficialBoard.com (the Site) is owned and operated by Alta Data (the Editor). The Privacy Policy covers the Site, its transactions, its electronic newsletters and its e-mails. Websites that have links on the Site may collect information about you on their websites. Their practices are not covered by this document.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a small piece of data sent to your Internet browser by a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data from your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system.

A Web beacon is a transparent graphic image, usually the size of a pixel, which is placed on a web site or in an e-mail to monitor the users’ behaviors.

We use cookies and web beacons to understand traffic patterns and to remember your membership status so that you don’t have to login each time you visit our site. We use those traffic data in an aggregate way on an anonymous basis.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies and web beacons and often display a warning before accepting them. However, if you refuse, you might not be able to use certain features of our site.

**IP addresses**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's address. This address is named "Internet Protocol" or IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Site. We read this information from your browser (information provided by every user’s browser). We also read the URL that you just came from and the URL you next go to. We use those traffic data on an anonymous basis in an aggregate way.

**Information we collect on our visitors and on our registered members**

When you register or provide information to the Site, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information.

Regarding your personally identifying information, we only collect those voluntarily provided by you such as your name, e-mail, your company, your title and your country of residence. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of our services by e-mail and to send you information you have requested.

Your personal information including your e-mail will not sold, rented, traded or posted to any third party except if required by law.

Credit card information will be processed only through PayPal or any similarly renowned worldwide financial institution. We do not keep any record regarding your credit card.

All your contribution to the Website will be kept for a maximum of 365 days and systematically discarded afterwards.

You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Website, but you will be unable to access certain services.

**Information collected on the Executives listed in the organizational charts**

Regarding company information and executive information, we only collect and post the publicly available and verifiable information voluntarily provided by our members such as company name, industry, website, country of registration, and such as executive name, title, business e-mail and reporting lines. We might also check and complete them through publicly available data from the company sites themselves or from renowned, reliable media.

We cover Executives belonging to companies with a revenue over 100 Millions US$ on three top reporting levels to ensure the public role of each Executive.

At any moment, any user can contact us to report an error at [contact@theofficialboard.com](mailto:contact@theofficialboard.com). If necessary, we will suspend the publication until we have carried out the right investigation.

**Control of your information**

At any time, Members may change their user profile and their preferences in their account or by following the instruction at the end of every email. Please change your password on a regular basis and do not share it with anyone. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information.

**Storage of your Personal Data**

After the closure of an account, all your personal information will be destroyed in the next 24 months.

**Email addresses**

We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, trade or post any e-mail address to any third-party except if requested by law. We only use email address to send information or contacts to our users. At any moment, any user can change his preference in his account.

**Third party service providers**

We occasionally hire third party companies to provide services on our behalf such as delivery of e-mailings or statistical analysis. We provide those companies with the minimum personal information they need to deliver the service. In some instances such as payments, the companies might collect the information directly from you and will notify you directly. In all cases, those companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information they collect from you and are prohibited to use it for any other purpose.

**Law request**

The Editor may disclose your personal information or your IP address if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such an action is necessary to: cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities; conform to the edicts of the law; comply with legal process served on the Site; identify persons who may be violating the law, the Terms of Use of the Site or the rights of third parties; protect the rights of the Site.

**Privacy under 18 years old**

You certify that you are 18 years old. We do not collect personally identifiable information for any person under 18 and do not allow anyone under 18 to be a member. If we learn we have collected any personal information from somebody under the age of 18 without the written consent of the parents, we will delete it from our database and cancel its access.

**Your consent**

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and the use of the information as specified in this Privacy Policy. We might amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check it periodically to always be aware of what we collect, use and disclose. The previous version will be kept for you on the site as a reference.

**To contact us**

If you have any question regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@theofficialboard.com](mailto:privacy@theofficialboard.com).
